cheap-domainregistration.com 2011-04-12

# Legal Agreement

Cheap Domain Registration Respects your privacy

**Other than as described in this Policy, we will not give any information about you to others without your express permission.**

**Information Collection and Use**

Our Site uses forms in which you give us contact information (including your name, address, telephone number, and email address) so you can place orders, request information and support, and make product suggestions. For certain services, we may also request a credit card number, government identification number, or other financial information. We will then create an account number for you.

We receive and store any information you enter on our Site or give us in any other way, including through email, telephone, or other communications with our customer service department. If you contact us for support, we will keep an internal record of what support was given.

We use your information to contact you regarding functionality changes to our products, our Site, new Cheap Domain Registration services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please see the "Updating Your Information" section below on how to change your preferences.

We may also use your information to present a co-branded offer with our partners or affiliates. If we collect information from you in connection with a co-branded offer, it will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the information and whose privacy statement applies.

We use information gathered about you from our Site statistics (for example, your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our Site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system.

Our Site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and receipts. We use cookies to identify you so you don't need to log in each time you visit our Site. The cookies are linked to your customer number, which is associated with the information in your account.

This Site also contains links to other websites. Unfortunately, Cheap Domain Registration is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

**Security**

This Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. 

**Updating Your Information**

You may alter your account information or opt out of receiving communications from us and our partners at any time. We have the following options for changing and modifying your account information or contact preferences.

  1. Visit your online [Account Manager](https://www.securepaynet.net/gdshop/shopper_lookup.asp?prog_id=domains)
  2. You may send mail to Cheap Domain Registration at the following postal address:   
14455 North Hayden Road, Suite 219, Scottsdale, AZ. 85260 USA 

**Sending Emails**

We use emails to communicate with you, to confirm your placed orders, and to send information that you have requested. We also provide email links, as on our ["About Us"](https://www.securepaynet.net/gdshop/about.asp?prog_id=domains) page, to allow you to contact us directly. We strive to promptly reply to your messages.

The information you send to us may be stored and used to improve this Site and our products, or it may be reviewed and discarded.

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. We will also share your information to the extent necessary to comply with ICANN's rules, regulations and policies.

**Third Party Service Providers**

We may at times provide information about you to third parties to provide various services on our behalf, such as processing credit card payments, serving advertisements, conducting contests or surveys, performing analyses of our products or customer demographics, shipping of goods or services, and customer relationship management. We will only share information about you that is necessary for the third party to provide the requested service. These companies are prohibited from retaining, sharing, storing or using your personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

In the event that we use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf, these companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gift or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, click [here. ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**Supplementation of Information**

In order to provide certain services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submit to us with information from third party sources ( _e.g.,_ information from our strategic partners, service providers, or the United States Postal Service).  We do this to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our products and services to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

**Contests/Surveys**

From time-to-time, we may provide you with the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys. If you choose to participate, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these contests or surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose the requested information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code and age level - note that you must be 18 or above to enter). We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor site traffic, and to personalize our Site.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests. When we do, that company will be prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

**Tell-A-Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service to inform a friend about our Site, we ask the user for the friend's name and email address. Cheap Domain Registration will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit our Site. Cheap Domain Registration stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact Cheap Domain Registration at to request the removal of this information from our database.

**What Happens to my Personal Information if I Terminate my Cheap Domain Registration Account?**

When your Cheap Domain Registration account is cancelled (either voluntarily or involuntarily) all of your personally identifiable information is placed in "deactivated" status on our relevant Cheap Domain Registration databases. However, deactivation of your account does not mean your personally identifiable information has been deleted from our database entirely. We will retain and use your personally identifiable information if necessary in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements.

**Changes in Our Practices**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and any other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page, at least thirty (30) days prior to the implementation of the changes.

**Contacting Our Site**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at:

* * *
